vidzbeez.com 2015-06-12

# iSpeed.club Guide

## Privacy Policy

**General**

iSpeed.club (“we” or “us”) is the owner of the website www.iSpeed.club ("the Site" or “iSpeed.club”). We understand you want to keep your information private, and that you value our emphasis on keeping your information safe and discrete. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you decide whether to use the Site and in what manner, and it describes how we collect, store and use information on individuals that use the Site. 

**Consent to use Information**

This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (“you” or “user”) and us. By accessing the Site, or providing information to us in other formats, you agree and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time and you consent to the collection and use of information in the manner set out in this Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy carefully and to periodically refer to it so that you understand it and its subsequent changes if any. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE STOP USING THE SITE IMMEDIATELY AND WHERE RELEVANT UNINSTALL .

**What Information Does the Site Collect?**

We collect two types of data and information from you:

**(a)** **the first type is** **Non-Personal Information** \- We retain some non-personally identifiable information (“Non-Personal Information”), such as your approximate geo-location, browser types, browser extensions, browser language, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us, operating system, your default browser and search providers, operating system language, and other information relating to your use of iSpeed.club in order to provide you with better services. 

**(b)** **The second type of information we collect is** **Personal Information** \- “Personal Information” is information that may be of a private or sensitive nature, identifies or may identify you. Some of the Personal Information is collected from you if you create an account on the Site and submit your information and some while you are using the Site. Such information may include your IP address, and your name, e-mail address and payment method info in case you provide us with this information (for instance when you open an account or if you approach us through the “contact us for” option).

We also treat any Non-personal Information which is specifically connected or linked to any Personal Information, as long as such connection or linkage exists, as Personal Information. ****

**What is the Purpose of Collecting Your Information?**

We collect the information detailed above in order to provide you with better services. Non-Personal Information is collected for research and statistical purposes, for enabling us to further develop, customize and improve iSpeed.club, based on your preferences, uses and interactions with iSpeed.club, and to provide you with the most relevant additional services and offers. 

In addition, our revenue model is designed so that iSpeed.club has 3rd party services implemented inside it for displaying advertisements and for providing with analytical services. We use your Non-Personal Information for the purpose of providing you with advertisements we or our partners think you may be interested in, including based on your statistical Non-Personal Information.

Your Personal Information is collected for a few purposes. First, it enables us to provide you with a better user experience and more relevant features, capabilities, offers and marketing materials. In addition, it allows us to provide you with technical assistance and support, and replying to questions and concerns received from you.

**Cookies**

Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file which is stored on your computer or device for the purpose of identifying the browser or product during interactions, remembering your preferences and collecting information about your activity on the Site. Detailed information about cookies and how we use them may be found in our **Cookies Policy** , which also describes how you can turn off cookies or to control which cookies are set on your computer or device. ****

**Who Receives Your Information?**

We may, and you approve us to share or transfer information, including Personal Information, internally within our group of companies. 

We share Non-Personally Information with third parties, when this is required in order to provide, maintain or improve our services and operation. This is the case with 3rd party advertisements; we share your Non-Personal Information with 3rd parties for the purpose of providing you with advertisements and offers we or such 3rd parties think you may be interested in, including based on your statistical Non-Personal Information. 

It is important to note that such 3rd party services may have their own privacy policies and we advise you to read them carefully. Inclusion of a link to third party website or service is not a recommendation of such a website or service. 3rd party sites may contain information or service that is illegal, unreasonable or that some people may find inappropriate or offensive. Before using third party sites and services or before making a purchase, we recommend you to read and understand those sites’, service’ or product’s terms and conditions, warranty, and privacy policies and to ensure you agree to their terms. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the products, services, or descriptions of those products or services that you receive from third party sites or to the content or privacy practices of those sites, and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any such third party products and services. You are knowingly and voluntarily assuming all risks of using third party sites to purchase products and services. You agree that we shall have no liability whatsoever with respect to such third party sites and your usage of them

We may also share your Personal Information and other information in special cases if we have a good reason to believe that it is necessary to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, violation of our policies or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any other agreements between you and iSpeed.club, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of iSpeed.club, its partners, its affiliates, users or the public.

**Review and Deletion**

We value your privacy and control over your personal information, and therefore you may notify us that you wish to either review your Personal Information or delete it. You can notify us by sending an email to [contact@iSpeed.club](mailto:contact@iSpeed.club). In order to delete or allow you to review your personal information, we may require that you provide us with identifying information or install additional software to allow such review. 

**Security and Confidentiality**

The collection and processing of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information is aimed at providing you with services offered by us and to send you commercial information on products or services we think you may be interested in. We will store this information as long as it is reasonably necessary to attain the mentioned purposes and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical requirement. 

We have security measures in place to prevent unauthorized access to and protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. 

If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our Policy, please contact us directly at [contact@iSpeed.club](mailto:contact@iSpeed.club) and our privacy officer shall investigate promptly.

**Children Protection**

We do not knowingly collect or store information regarding children under the age of 13.

**Information Warranty Disclaimer**

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness and security of any of the information we gather, store and disclose to you or to anyone else.

**Change of Ownership**

In the event of a change of ownership or control of all or part of iSpeed.club, including without limitation through acquisition, merger or sale, we reserve the right to sell all or part of the Personal Information and Non-Personal Information we store in our systems. You acknowledge that in the event of bankruptcy, insolvency or receivership, we may have no control over the use and transfer of your personal information. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Policy may be revised from time to time at our sole discretion, so please check it regularly. The last revision will be reflected in the "Last modified by" heading.

**Cookies Policy**

Last modified on 19 June 2014

When visiting the Site, we send “cookies” to your device. Cookies are small files of code, usually stored on a user's computer or device, which enable a website to "personalize" itself for each user and remember his preferences. Most websites that you visit today will use cookies in one way or another in order to improve your user experience. Similarly, we have placed cookies on your computer to improve your experience using iSpeed.club. You can change your cookie settings at any time, but otherwise, we will assume you are OK to continue.

**What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are text strings of information that are downloaded to your computer or device when you are using iSpeed.club. Your web browser then sends these cookies back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes those cookies. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and making the interaction between you and the Site quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help ensure that the advertisements you see are relevant to you and your interests.

**Different Types of Cookies**

There are four main types of cookie we use:

**Strictly necessary cookies:** These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around and use the features of a website, or to provide a service requested by you. We do not need to obtain your consent in order to use these cookies. ****

**Functionality cookies:** These cookies allow the Site to remember choices you make (such as your account name, language or the region you are in) and provide more personal and enhanced features.  For instance, a website may be able to provide you with more localized information or products by using a cookie to store information about the region in which you are currently located, remember changes you have made to text or view size, and other parts of web pages that you can customize, and provide services you have asked for.

**Performance cookies:** These cookies collect information about how you use the Site, for instance which pages you go to most often, and if you get error messages from them. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies you. All of the information collected by these cookies is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how the Site works.

**Targeting cookies or advertising cookies:** These cookies are used to deliver adverts that are more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the permission of a website’s operator. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization. For more information about online behavioral advertising cookies and online privacy, please see the guide produced by the internet advertising industry available at [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

**How to Manage Your Cookie Settings**

There are various ways in which you can manage and control your cookie settings.

**You should bear in mind that, by deleting or blocking cookies, some or all of the websites you visit (or features of them) may not work properly or as effectively.**

**Turning Off Cookies via Your Web Browser**

Most web browsers will provide you with some general information about cookies, enable you to see what cookies you’ve got, allow you to delete them all or on an individual basis, and enable you block or allow cookies for all websites or individually selected websites. You can also normally turn off third party advertising cookies separately. 

**Please note that if you adjust your cookie settings via your web browser then, unless you delete or block each cookie individually, the changes will apply to all websites that you visit – not just our Site. You will also need to adjust your cookies on a browser-by-browser basis.   **

Information about cookies is usually found in the “Help” section of the web browser. Below are some links to the “Help” sections of some commonly used web browsers:

Internet Explorer - <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955>

Windows Phone - <http://www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx>

Google Chrome - [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)

Google Android - <http://support.google.com/android/?hl=en>

Mozilla Firefox - [http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Cookies](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Cookies)

Opera - <http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>

Safari - <http://www.apple.com/support/safari/> 

**Turning Off Third Party Cookies**

You will have the option of turning off third party targeting/advertising cookies each time you see an advertisement that has been personalized to you.

Some advertising networks that partner with us may use cookies to better manage advertising campaigns, specifically to personalize advertising messages and to impose frequency caps. 

**Note that the third party listed above may need to set a cookie in order to remember that their targeting/advertising cookies should not be assigned to you in the future. If you change or delete your browser’s cookie file, or change or upgrade your browser or Device, then you might need to opt out again.**
